Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trial, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
After the Magic Knights awards ceremony, the grand finale of the Star Festival,
the nation's king delivered an announcement of monumental importance.
We have located the Midnight Sun's hideout!
To combat this deadly fall, we're planning to gather the absolute cream of the crap from the Magic Knight Swords!
They'll be the Royal Knights!
And while Yuno and Osta were making sense of the news...
Damn you! You wicked little imbecile!
They happen to run into the new captain of the Crimson Lion Kings, Meraleona Vermillion,
marating her squad members in a demonic rage.
The Magic Rage
May I have this 직업 next to yourца?
Boy, you don't seem to know what to do
I've just seen some beta Doctor where I was playing
It doesn't work with you
確かなものを追い求めてさ
どこへ行くの?
履き潰した靴のレッシュアート
出発で一体どこだっけな
いつかのページがひらくった
言い訳ばかり探している
毎日にさよなら
助けるよ
走り出す列車に乗り乗った
小さくては見えないけど
大丈夫さ
そんな気がするんだ
これを迎えあった
Frater Stultum is currently out of commission?!
You feckless little invents!
What's a Frater Stultum?
Idiot brother.
Who is she talking about, though?
Foygolion, of course.
Wait a second! Are you trying to tell me that this crazy lady is related to Foygolion and Leo?!
They're siblings?!
That brother of mine has always been a buffoon!
How could he have produced such a pack of cowards?!
And now I have the pleasure of looking after you sad sex while he's off taking a nap!
Foygolion's not fit to be your captain!
Hold on, that's not true!
My brother was the finest captain we ever could have asked for!
That's right! Captain Foygolion was a perfect example of the kind of person that every magic knight should aspire to be!
He cared about every member of this squad in the Clover Kingdom more than anyone else I've met in my life!
If you ask me, that man's the greatest magic knight in this whole country!
That's why I refuse to let you talk about him that way!
Even if you are-
Well, if you feel that strongly about it, then you'd better give me less talk and more action!
Show me you're the strongest team in the kingdom, led by the strongest captain!
That numbskull isn't going to die?!
That would mean abandoning his country and the Crimson Lion Kings!
So until he returns, I want every one of you to walk with pride and show the world the full glory of our mighty ranks!
It's my job to work you to the bone while my brother's away, and that's exactly what I plan to do!
Don't you dare let me down!
Yes, ma'am!
Did you hear that, Yuno?
Man, she is on fire!
Tell me about it.
What kind of training is she going to make him do?
Now then, off to the Hot Springs training camp.
Hot Springs, seriously?
Hot Springs?
Hot Springs, really?
Hot Springs, seriously?
Whoa, that sounds like the funnest training camp in the world!
And the easiest.
I heard that.
You're coming with us, kid.
How does that work?
You trying to kidnap me?
I mean, not that I wouldn't love to, but we're from different schools!
You're coming with us, kid.
How does that work?
You trying to kidnap me?
I mean, not that I wouldn't love to, but we're from different schools!
I wouldn't love to, but we're from different squads, and it's dangerous to go places with strangers, so...
Hey, Asta!
Are you going to join our squad and be my official rival?
No!
I'm out.
This doesn't involve me.
Later.
Yuno, wait!
Don't leave me!
Both of you.
Uh-oh.
Hey, cut it out, you big hothead!
Yuno's not interested in your little spa trip, so get your hands off of that!
It's not a spa trip!
Look, Belle.
I'd rather you stay out of this.
You'll only make her more heated.
Kate, if you say so!
Once my sister sinks her claws into you, there's no hope of escaping.
She doesn't care for war.
She's not interested in politics.
That's why she never really took center stage in our family.
But when she does fight, she's arguably stronger than our brother.
They call her the uncrowned, undefeated lioness, Meryl Leona Vermillion!
And I think I'll call you rookies one and two.
Now let's hit the hot springs and see what you're made of.
I don't know why, but I got a bad feeling about this!
Whoa, that drink tasted like victory!
She feels good to outrank every magic knight in this whole bar!
Are you feeling okay, Char?
Call me Captain.
Captain.
You got it, Char.
Don't get all cocky just because you managed to win for once after a lifetime of bringing
up the rear, sucky hero.
Must be rough for you getting your ass handed to you by the squad that always comes in dead
last!
Shut your filthy mouth or I'll shut it for you!
That's a pretty fancy hairdo you sporting there, Mr. Silver Eagles!
You must think very highly of yourself for a guy who got beat by the black bulls.
Good for you!
Oh, you wanna do this?
Mercury magic!
Silver spears!
My apologies, sir.
We don't allow offensive spells in the bar.
Here's a drink on the house for the inconvenience.
Sorry, I wasn't aware.
Delicious.
The barkeep is right, Nozel.
This is a place for enjoying drinks, not for fighting.
You shouldn't have missed the event.
It was quite unbecoming.
Your hairdo might be even stupider than his!
I'll make you eat those words, you ruffian!
Nope.
I'm sorry, sir.
As I told the other gentleman, no offensive magic inside.
Please accept a free drink.
Oh, my goodness.
It must have slipped my mind.
Do forgive me.
And thank you for this.
Upon my word.
Don't you clowns know how to stand up for yourselves?
Looks like it's my turn.
Yeah.
On second thought, I guess I could let it go.
Why is everybody acting so damn reasonable now?
Those bartenders gotta be putting some sketchy happy drugs in those cocktails of his.
Captain Yami!
I really look up to you.
I mean, I only came in last place this one time and look how busted up I let myself get!
But you were in dead last like forever and you never lost your cool.
That's like superhuman or something.
You really are amazing.
You're so confident, so thick skinned, you don't care how much people laugh at you.
Even though you were always the worst, you did everything your way.
Thank you.
For the last time, I don't understand anything you're saying to me.
Cat, you just wait until next year.
Oh, come on, you really leaving?
What's wrong, Beanpole?
Any other day you'd be begging me to go drink with you.
Shut it!
Suit yourself.
I guess that means I'll be knocking back the celebratory booze without you.
You sure are riding high for a one-time winner.
Huh?
Oh, Sisgolion.
Where do you get that name from?
You're Fwigolion's sister, so I assumed that was right.
You honestly believe a lineage as proud as mine would name their offspring so carelessly?
You don't?
I figured you'd just take whatever thing you are and slap a Golion on the end of it.
You're such a simpleton.
Oh, hey, how's it going, Captain?
Looks like she got a hold of you, kid. How'd that happen anyway?
Ah, that's kind of a long story.
You're coming, too.
Being late's bad enough, but you didn't even show up.
Hey, wait, wait, stop it.
You need to learn a little discipline.
Discipline? Well, I'm already the captain!
Sorry, Yami, but it serves you right.
You two!
You're not taking my Char anywhere!
And who are you?
Don't worry, Char.
I may not know what's going on, but I'd follow you anywhere in the universe!
For the last time, it's Captain.
Asta, so this is where you've been hiding.
Listen, it's not like you were the reason we came in second.
So dispense with the celebrating and help me give Kahono and Kyoto a proper send-off.
Oh, Mary Leona.
Oh, it's been too long.
Well, have a nice night.
Uh-uh.
Noelle?
Um, yes, ma'am?
You're coming, too.
Wait, wait a minute! You can't be serious!
I don't have anything to do with this nonsense!
Yeah, and how many fiery cat paws can this lady possibly have?!
But why me? It's not fair.
Don't be a baby!
Do you have any idea where she's taking us?
A hot spring, I think?
A hot spring?
Oh, hey there, Noelle. Could you wash my back for me?
You're such a fervor!
I him?!
All of you, settle down!
Uh-uh!
Thank you for your patronage.
Well, how do you like that?
It looks like things are about to get more interesting.
What the...? This is the hot spring?
What's the hold-up?! Let's get to work!
Yuletim Volcano is a strong magic region.
Deep underground, there's a volcanic belt that's laced with mana and constantly spewing out lava.
Normal humans can't set foot in this place.
But if you reach the peak, you'll find the most fantastic and revitalizing hot spring you can imagine.
How's that?!
Are you getting excited?!
Come! Let's head for the summit!
I wouldn't say excited!
No way! This place is a nightmare!
Then again...
Sol, please wash my back.
A hot spring with Char?! Sweet!
Look, Sol, there was really no reason for you to tag along with us.
What are you talking about?! I told you I'd follow you anywhere so this'll be easy as pie!
Okay, Char?
Call me Captain.
Roger, Char!
I say we make it a race to see which one of us can get to the summit first! Are you game, Asuna?!
Sure, I can stand to blow off some steam!
I'm ready when you are!
Hey, Golden Boy!
Are you in or what?
Knock yourselves out.
Oh right, he's Mr. Cool.
Killjoy.
Yeah, but you get used to it.
Quick wasting time and let's go!
Alright, time to do this!
Poor magic to do the trick!
What's the deal with this heat?
The mana in the atmosphere is going crazy!
I'm suffocating!
It's hard to breathe!
I feel like my chest is on fire and my sweat glands are about to explode!
And on top of that, she expects us to climb an erupting volcano?! There's just no way!
No way!
If I try to duck out, Siskoleon's gonna come after me again.
I guess I'm doing this.
Why did she insist on bringing me?
It's a good thing I'm starting to sober up.
If I fail, I'll be a disgrace to women everywhere.
Let's make this quick!
Wow, the captains are unbelievably strong!
It's like the magma's not even affecting them!
Yeah, but they shouldn't be able to move like that in this environment!
It's not humanly possible!
So cool!
I think I know!
They're both using Monaskin!
To some extent, all magic knights use magic power to enhance their physical abilities in combat situations.
But the height of this skill is a fundamental spell known as Monaskin.
Even in unstable conditions such as these, Yami and Charlotte are able to emit a constant stream of magic power
that encases their body and protects them from damage.
Monaskin!
That's nothing!
Every magic knight knows how to use a basic technique like that!
Yeah, but not everybody can sustain it for that long in a raging volcano.
There's no way we'll make it!
Of course we will!
All we have to do is feel it out as we go, slowly adapt to the mana here.
Then make our way up to the summit before our magic power runs out!
We've gone soft, so think of this as a chance to retrain ourselves!
You ready?
Ready!
Aw, gross! It's so hot!
Monaskin, huh?
I feel like my body's gonna burn to a minute!
Let me get out of here!
Aw, this feels much better!
Hey, Yuno!
Hurry or I'll be dizzy from the hot spring before you even get there!
Well, I'm heading up! See ya!
Leo!
Dammit, Yuno! You better wait for me!
I'm gonna be as strong as Char is!
And then the two of us can relax in the hot spring together!
I get it now.
Siskoleon brought us out here so we could be examples for the Crimson Lion Kings.
Especially Charlotte.
Her magic's an awful fit for a place like this, but she's still holding her own.
When the little Golden Dawn prodigy is their age, that'll probably get them feeling competitive.
Huh. The boss lady of theirs is sharper than she lets on.
I thought I told you, louse! Quit dawdling and move it!
Or maybe she's just mean. I don't know anymore.
Monaskin, it's not exactly an easy thing to pull off if you have a hard time controlling your magic power.
And my water magic is practically made for these conditions.
It's been forever since I'd seen Mara Leona.
And she tracks me to this place? She must really hate me.
You say something, Noelle?
Gah! Me? No, not a word!
Are you ready to climb?
I asked if you were ready to climb!
I am!
You used to be a little girl who feared her siblings.
But I can tell from your mana, that's changed.
That's changed.
It's not just your outward appearance.
You resemble her on the inside a little too.
She was a powerful magic knight,
and possessed an incredibly strong heart as well.
Unlike anyone I've ever met.
Thank you for the beautiful flowers.
I hear you'll be giving birth any day now.
Yes.
And afterwards, are you considering returning to the field of battle?
This is no time to cry!
So the children have already told you.
Lady Osir, the magic knights need you to return to your post as soon as you recover.
I honestly don't understand why you would put your life in such danger.
I know I don't need to remind you,
but once the magic knights decide to enter the fray,
they will never stop fighting in order to protect the Clover Kingdom and its people,
even if it means they must put their own lives on the line.
You see, having a child is no different.
When a woman is carrying a baby,
she'll do whatever's necessary to prevent any harm from befalling that innocent life.
That's what being a mother is, Mary Leona.
There's nothing stronger than a determined woman,
and your mother was certainly that.
If you have the determination to reach the top,
then there's no mountain in existence that you can't conquer.
Yes, ma'am!
They're gone.
Everyone's way up ahead.
My muscles and spirit are just about shot.
They're gone.
Everyone's way up ahead.
My muscles and spirit are just about shot.
The heat is too strong for my sword to cut through.
I don't think I can get up there after all.
They're gone.
Everyone's way up ahead.
My muscles and spirit are just about shot.
The heat is too strong for my sword to cut through.
I don't think I can get up there after all.
Then quit.
It was a fool's errand for someone without magic to attempt to scale this mountain at all.
And here I was thinking rookie number two might actually have something going for him.
Now I see you've only come this far because fortune's been on your side.
At least you have that.
Even if you aren't able to overcome this trial.
You might just end up being the next wizard king through nothing but sheer luck of the draw.
Do yourself a favor.
Climb down.
I'm not leaving.
What I want.
I'm just wondering how can I become the wizard king.
What we want most in the world.
Is it something you can just achieve through blind luck.
It's about results.
Yeah?
Then you better get moving.
A noble heart alone cannot protect anyone.
And the trust of the people is earned, not granted.
You want to know what you need to do to gain the title of wizard king?
I don't see how a fool who doesn't even know himself can achieve anything great.
Get results.
Prove that you're the strongest.
I'll reach the top.
Our trade depends on it.
You want results.
You got it.
What else you'd like doing to dress a lot?
OK.
Doesn't it come out you?
It's exactly just fun.
You'll all know what you're doing.
That won't.
I'm going THERE!
You will find a recognise with whoever has an end Ellish family.
Grab the house Let us.
Xiad такой...
even if you love a cloud with Kyat2итель.
I'll support someone who is wearing explanations and not to need them.
If you run a fool by her,
you will melt the floor from anywhere else.
I'll make it true
My song, my days
This world will響かせ yukou
I'll make it true
My song, my days
音符を書き加えてく
流りくなった道さの空には
輝ける明日を映すメロディー
Cloverclips
A Dialogue with Dorothy
Hey, Dorothy
How about a little conversation?
I was wondering if you have any hobbies
other than sleeping when you're standing up
Oh, I bet you I can guess
Maybe you like taking dancing lessons
And you probably enjoy cooking meals
Your best dish is hamburger
But sometimes you prefer to cook up dessert
I'd love to sample your cooking one day, Dorothy
Hey, how about we play rock, paper, scissors
And if I win, you cook for me
This ought to be easy
One, two, three
How dare you weaklings call yourselves magic knights
Don't give up
And soon we'll bask in that glorious hot spring
Black Clover, page 72
St. Elmo's 5
My magic is uninhibited naked conversation
Yay
questions
To be continued
We'll be later
Bye